<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Podcast List</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Podcast List</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/compressedfm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/compressedfm/</guid>
      <description>COMPRESSEDfm A weekly podcast about web design and development with a little zest from James Q Quick, Amy Dutton, Brad Garropy, and Bekah HW.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/contejas-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/contejas-code/</guid>
      <description>ConTejas Code ConTejas Code is a podcast in the web engineering space that has deep dives on various topics between frontend engineering with React, TypeScript, Next.js, and backend engineering with Kafka, Postgres, and more. The series is a mix of long-form content and guest episodes with industry leaders in the web engineering space.From the podcast, listeners will take away actionable best practices that you can integrate into your workflows as well as valuable insights from prominent people in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/syntax-tasty-web-development-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/syntax-tasty-web-development-treats/</guid>
      <description>Syntax - Tasty Web Development Treats Full Stack Developers Wes Bos and Scott Tolinski dive deep into web development topics, explaining how they work and talking about their own experiences. They cover from JavaScript frameworks like React, to the latest advancements in CSS to simplifying web tooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/talk-python-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/talk-python-to-me/</guid>
      <description>Talk Python To Me Talk Python to Me is a weekly podcast hosted by developer and entrepreneur Michael Kennedy. We dive deep into the popular packages and software developers, data scientists, and incredible hobbyists doing amazing things with Python. If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Python, you&amp;rsquo;ll quickly learn the ins and outs of the community by hearing from the leaders. And if you&amp;rsquo;ve been Pythoning for years, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn about your favorite packages and the hot new ones coming out of open source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/that/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcasts/that/</guid>
      <description>THAT Welcome to THAT, a daily podcast hosted by Clark Sell and the crew at THAT Conference.&#xA;Our goal with this podcast is simple. I want to tell your story. I want to document these experiences in such that we can all help one another. I know that sounds a bit abstract, but over the years, I’ve talked with thousands of professionals who all have an awesome and unique story. I’ve loved hearing every one of them, and they’ve each inspired me in some way.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
